{
    "subject": "resource/WFLZ-FM",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "WFLZ-FM (93.3 FM, \"93-3 FLZ\")  is a CHR/Pop station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA. The station has a class C signal operating at 100,000 watts effective radiated power, and is one of the most powerful FM radio stations in Florida, covering four of the state's radio markets.  The station's studios are located in South Tampa and the transmitter site is in Riverview.WFLZ currently broadcasts in HD format.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about WFLZ-FM is that it's a CHR/Pop station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8416550755500793,
            "question": "In which state is WFLZ-FM broadcasting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7694128155708313,
            "question": "Is WFLZ-FM a local or national station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7583842277526855,
            "question": "Where is WFLZ-FM located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.73478102684021,
            "question": "Are there any other radio stations in Tampa Bay that play similar music to WFLZ-FM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7202259302139282,
            "question": "What makes a radio station successful in the Tampa Bay area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5460931062698364,
            "question": "What type of music does WFLZ-FM play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4997577667236328,
            "question": "What does CHR stand for in relation to radio stations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49860432744026184,
            "question": "Can you name some popular artists typically played on a CHR/Pop station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4916195273399353,
            "question": "What is the general target audience for a CHR/Pop station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3415607213973999,
            "question": "How has the popularity of CHR/Pop music changed over time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about WFLZ-FM is that it's a CHR/Pop station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4398_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the general target audience for a CHR/Pop station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4398_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some popular artists typically played on a CHR/Pop station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4398_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does CHR stand for in relation to radio stations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4398_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4398_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indeed provide information supporting that WFLZ-FM is a CHR/Pop station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information provided earlier states that WFLZ-FM played the oldies format before switching to Top 40, but it does not mention CHR/Pop.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}